Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCIX is arranged in 7 sub-series by Union file number.
Series C is arranged in 228 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCIX. 1947 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 492-0. 1947 Convention. General
    - General, 1945-1950 (Box 612, Folder 1)
    - General, 1947 (Box 612, Folder 2)
    - Speakers, 1947-1948 (Box 612, Folder 3)
    - List of Delegates, 1947 (Box 612, Folder 4)
    - Auxiliary Section., 1946-1947 (Box 612, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 492-1. 1947 Convention. Constitution.
    - Report of Committee on Legislation., 1947 (Box 612, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations for changes in Grand Lodge Constitution and Laws, 1946-1948 (Box 612, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 492-2. 1947 Convention. Hotel Reservations
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 612, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 492-3. 1947 Convention. Resolutions
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 612, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 492-4. 1947 Convention. Committee Appointments
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 612, Folder 10-12)
  - Sub-Series 492-5. 1947 Convention. Transportation.
    - Pullman Rates, 1947 (Box 612, Folder 13)
      June 3, 1947-December 1947.
  - Sub-Series 492-7. 1947 Convention. Grand President's Convention Report
    - General, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 1-13)
- Series C. 1947 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 500-0. 1947 Convention Resolutions. General
    - Resolutions Nos. 1-227, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 4)
    - Resolutions Nos. 1-227, 1947-1948 (Box 613, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 500-1. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 1
    - Delete "From Whence We Came or Whither We Are Going" from Ritual, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 500-2. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 2
    - Administer Obligation to Chairmen of Local Protective Committee, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 500-3. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 3
    - Amend Ritual to provide installation ceremony for Chairman of Local Protective Committee, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 500-4. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 4
    - To increase mileage and per diem allowance to Delegates of 1947 Convention (Box 613, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 500-5. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 5
    - To increase mileage and per diem allowance to Convention Delegates, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 500-6. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 6
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 500-7. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 7
    - To amend the Unemployment Insurance Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 500-8. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 8
    - To support the Crosser Amendments to the Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Acts, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 500-9. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 9
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 500-10. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 10
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 500-11. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 11
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947-1949 (Box 613, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 500-12. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 12
    - To provide benefits similar to Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Acts for employees of bus and truck industry, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 500-13. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 13
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 500-14. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 14
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 500-15. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 15
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947-1949 (Box 613, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 500-16. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 16
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 500-17. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 17
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 500-18. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 18
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 500-19. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 19
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 500-20. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 20
    - To amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 500-21. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 21
    - To provide grab-irons or steps in bunkers of refrigerator cars, 1947-1954 (Box 613, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 500-22. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 22
    - To establish a National Labor Supreme Court, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 500-23. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 23
    - To extend Federal Employers' Liability Act to include employees of Railway Express Agency, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 500-24. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 24
    - To establish differential wage for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 500-25. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 25
    - Grand Lodge to establish standard form for handling grievances, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 500-26. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 26
    - Grand President to devise a model Agreement, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 500-27. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 27
    - To secure 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 500-28. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 28
    - To place all excepted positions under all rules or relinquish jurisdiction, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 500-29. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 29
    - All Railway Express Agents at depots where fewer than 10 are employed to be placed under Clerks' Agreement, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 500-30. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 30
    - Instruct Grand President to obtain the same pass privileges for Express employees as are granted railroad employees, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 500-31. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 31
    - Express Messengers to be paid overtime for work in excess of 176 hours per month, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 500-32. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 32
    - Grand President to undertake to correct conditions in Express cars, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 500-33. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 33
    - To amend Section 6 of Railway Labor Act, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 500-34. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 34
    - All System Boards to serve notice for 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 500-35. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - 40-hour week with 48 hours' pay, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 500-36. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 36
    - To form more Ladies' Auxiliaries, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 500-37. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 37
    - Canadian System Boards to be composed of Officers, District Chairmen and Local Chairmen, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 500-38. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 38
    - Strive for union shop, 1947-1950 (Box 613, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 500-39. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 39
    - All Agreements to be ratified by membership, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 500-40. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 40
    - To oppose Government-controlled strike vote in Canada, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 500-41. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 41
    - Support the union of all labor organizations to form a Canadian Labour Party, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 500-42. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 42
    - To bring about unity of all labor organizations., 1947 (Box 613, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 500-43. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 43
    - To conclude revision of Canadian Pension Plan, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 500-44. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 44
    - Sick leave and vacation for Canadian employees, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 500-45. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 45
    - Stabilization of employment, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 500-46. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 46
    - Pension legislation for Canadians, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 500-47. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 47
    - To oppose anti-labor legislation in United States and Canada, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 500-48. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 48
    - To establish a nationwide strike fund, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 500-49. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 49
    - To elect a full-time District Chairman in British Columbia, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 500-50. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 50
    - To affiliate American Federation of Labor with World Federation of Labor Unions., 1947 (Box 613, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 500-51. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 51
    - To establish minimum of 8 hours at time and one-half for Sunday work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 500-52. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 52
    - Vacations to be granted on seniority basis; 160-day provision to be eliminated, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 500-53. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 53
    - 12 days' vacation for all based on seniority, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 500-54. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 54
    - Differential rate for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 500-55. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 55
    - Sick leave benefits, 1947-1948 (Box 613, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 500-56. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 56
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 500-57. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 57
    - Change period for seniority benefits, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 500-58. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 58
    - List exceptions to rules following the rule, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 500-59. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 59
    - Place scheduled positions on excepted list, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 500-60. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 60
    - Differential rate for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 500-61. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 61
    - To include all Canadian Express workers, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 500-62. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 62
    - Extra pay for employees required to work positions to which not regularly assigned, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 500-63. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 63
    - Pay for holiday not worked, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 500-64. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 64
    - Start and end shift at same point, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 500-65. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 65
    - Employee to be paid full rate while qualifying, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 500-66. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 66
    - Life membership for Fitzgerald, E.H., 1947 (Box 613, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 500-67. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 67
    - Differential pay for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 500-68. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 68
    - Payment to messengers handling United States Mail, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 500-69. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 69
    - Liberalize free transportation, 1947-1948 (Box 613, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 500-70. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 70
    - National sick leave rule, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 500-71. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 71
    - Time and one-half for all Sunday work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 500-72. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 72
    - Grand Lodge to subscribe to "Labor" for all members, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 500-73. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 73
    - Time and one-half for all Sunday work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 500-74. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 74
    - Reduce retirement age, 1947-1951 (Box 613, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 500-75. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 75
    - Equalize rates of pay, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 500-76. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 76
    - 6 days' notice of reduction in force, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 500-77. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 77
    - Differential pay for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 500-78. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 78
    - All Agreements to be ratified by members, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 500-79. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 79
    - To oppose anti-labor legislation (21 United), 1947 (Box 613, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 500-80. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 80
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 500-81. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 81
    - Recording secretaries to accept subscription to "Labor" in groups of ten or more at reduced rates, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 500-82. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 82
    - Differential rate for night work, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 500-83. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 83
    - Married women to be laid off instead of others regardless of seniority, 1947-1949 (Box 613, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 500-84. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 84
    - To stipulate payday, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 500-85. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 85
    - 40-hour week; increased vacations., 1947 (Box 613, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 500-86. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 86
    - To establish uniform wage scale, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 500-87. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 87
    - Vacations and sick leave for veterans, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 500-88. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 88
    - Express Agency to pay time and one-half for all willful violations of rules, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 500-89. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 89
    - To establish mileage rate for Express Messengers, 1947-1948 (Box 613, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 500-90. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 90
    - Railway Express Agency to pay penalty rate for violation of rules, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 500-91. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 91
    - Vacations for veterans, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 500-92. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 92
    - Business of System Boards to be handled on proportional basis, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 500-93. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 93
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 98)
  - Sub-Series 500-94. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 94
    - Payment for vacations not obtained by deceased employees, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 99)
  - Sub-Series 500-95. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 95
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 500-96. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 96
    - Vacation year to be between May 1 and September 1, 1947 (Box 613, Folder 101)
  - Sub-Series 500-97. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 97
    - National Agreement on wages and rules, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 500-98. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 98
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 500-99. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 99
    - To oppose anti-labor Congressmen, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 500-100. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 100
    - Differential pay for night work, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 500-101. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 101
    - Railroad Employees to be paid extra for Handling Pullman Company business, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 500-102. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 102
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 500-103. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 103
    - Sick leave with pay, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 500-104. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 104
    - National Sick Leave Rule, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 500-105. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 105
    - Differential pay for night work, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 500-106. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 106
    - Retroactive pay adjustments to apply to members only, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 500-107. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 107
    - To amend Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 500-108. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 108
    - To establish a National Sick Leave Rule, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 500-109. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 109
    - Reaffirm Resolution adopted at St. Louis, Missouri in 1943, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 500-110. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 110
    - Memorial to members losing their lives in World War II, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 500-111. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 111
    - 40-hour week; night differential; equalization of rates; liberalize Vacation Agreement, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 500-112. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 112
    - Restore pension rights lost by Canadians in Strike of 1918, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 500-113. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 113
    - Amend Vacation Agreement; establish Sick Leave Rule; pay for holidays (double-time if worked); differential for night work; 40-hour week, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 500-114. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 114
    - Define vacation for each month worked; union shop, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 500-115. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 115
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 500-116. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 116
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 500-117. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 117
    - Eliminate Auxiliary Lodges and issue Brotherhood Charters, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 500-118. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 118
    - Continue separate Lodges and grant full rights to Colored members, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 500-119. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 119
    - Grand President to render an account of vote taken in ratification of Legislative Board Laws, 1947-1949 (Box 614, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 500-120. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 120
    - Delegates not receiving free transportation to be reimbursed, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 500-121. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 121
    - To revise Sick Leave Rule, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 500-122. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 122
    - Convention to define "fitness and ability", 1947 (Box 614, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 500-123. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 123
    - Grand Lodge to provide printed form to be used in securing wage data, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 500-124. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 124
    - To eliminate holiday restriction on passes, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 500-125. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 125
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 29-30)
  - Sub-Series 500-126. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 126
    - To discontinue practice of requiring employees to return to work before being paid for vacation, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 500-127. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 127
    - Heirs of deceased employees to be paid for vacations not obtained before death, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 500-128. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 128
    - 6 additional days' vacation after 25 years' seniority, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 500-129. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 129
    - Retire at 60 after 30 years' service, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 500-130. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 130
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide increased annuities, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 500-131. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 131
    - Compulsory retirement at 70 years, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 500-132. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 132
    - Commending Grand Lodge Officers for passage of Crosser Act, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 500-133. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 133
    - All railroad L.C.L. business to be handled by Railway Express Agency, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 500-134. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 134
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 500-135. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 135
    - Increase vacation on basis of service, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 500-136. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 136
    - Require General Chairmen to attend at least one regular meeting of each lodge each year, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 500-137. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 137
    - Correct method of settling personal injury claims, 1947-1949 (Box 614, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 500-138. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 138
    - Establish minimum pension of $100 per month, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 500-139. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 139
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 500-140. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 140
    - Equalize rates in Chicago Switching District, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 45)